It's a new year, it's a new year, it's a new year
It's nothing, nothing, it's nothing today
Let's make it fun!
Wow!
踊る風に誘われた 坂道の向こう側に
どこまでも広がる青 目を奪われて
音を立て トキメキの予感
真っ白な秘めた気持ちが 色づいてゆく
最後は君と紡いでいく未来
今はまだかさぐりで迷っても
頬物で描き出す光
眠い色の明日が呼んでる
道知るってなくたって
不安な音
分け合って君がいる
いつだってほら笑って
ハイファイブ!
ご視聴ありがとうございました
How cute.
Yeah, I'd kill for that precious bean.
I bet that made you really happy.
Totally.
I sleep with it every night.
And I put the putty kura he gave me in my phone case.
Very romantic.
So, which one is Gojo?
Obvi, the one that's a total smoke show.
Duh.
Putty cutie pie.
We had the pleasure of meeting him on Halloween.
Seems like a very nice young man.
No fair.
I want to skip around in a school uniform and have sexy guys win these stuff.
And put one on and go skip.
You can totally pull it off, King.
Aw, jeez.
Then I might try.
Fine, but this plan requires a hot and willing participant.
What a dream-o, evil setmother!
Dream away.
I already have something in mind for my next date ensemble!
Do tell.
A pair of loose socks.
Cutesy, huh?
And hot, too.
I know what you're talking about.
Those were in style ages ago.
Yeah, but they're making a comeback.
Kids love them.
I saw a girl wearing them at our school festival.
They were low-key fire.
I wonder if part of their appeal is that they're such a blast from the past.
Nostalgia.
It rules.
It's so...
Fetch!
Just sit back and relax.
KK!
Do you want to have your nails done today, too?
For sure.
Hatta, girl.
A matte look would be nice for the winter.
What's with the staring?
Not to be rude, but have you gained weight?
Huh?
You're a model!
You're living the dream, so you better take it seriously!
Geez, who's the evil stepmother this time, you old hag?
Hmm.
It isn't much.
You just look fuller.
I do?
Hmm.
Well, I don't see any difference.
Really?
Maybe I'm losing it.
It was so sweet!
He won this plushie and gave it to me!
Look at it!
Adores!
Oh, he brought home the bacon!
So squishy!
You are such a girly girl, Maureen.
I bet you cuddle that poor thing to death!
Great job today, everyone!
And great job to you, too!
You did some of your best work out there, Rana.
Rana, it feels like you're getting cuter every day.
You really think so?
I agree!
She was literally glowing!
Your cheeks were pinker than usual and super shiny!
Come jelly, you're like a freaking cherub!
You don't know?
Huh?
Apparently, Rana has a new boo thing!
Are you for serious?
I'm sorry I was too embarrassed to tell you!
He came to watch a shoot one time and he was a total hottie.
Show me!
Maureen needs a selfie!
Stacked!
Right.
I'm getting major protagonist good guy hero vibes from him,
but what exactly is happening here?
It's the time Kay very sweetly tried and failed
to make me pancakes for breakfast.
Being in love always makes a girl feel pretty.
It starts inside and radiates out.
Wait, does that actually happen?
Yup!
My sweet little sister has fallen head over heels for this idol.
All of a sudden, she has a new sparkle!
She loves traveling to watch the shows.
Oh my gosh, that is the best thing ever!
I would follow all my faves far and wide.
Love makes you feel like you can do anything!
Maureen?
Yes?
Is she asking about me?
Of course!
I've been crushing stupid hard lately!
Is it showing in my pictures?
How embarrassing!
I could die!
Maureen, sweetheart, you've gained weight!
Huh?
You really think I have?
Your face has gotten a little bit rounder.
We'll start shooting for the summer editions any day now.
And you'll have to show more skin.
You know what you have to do.
Figure it out, dear.
I guess it's true.
Honestly, when I look at myself, I feel the same.
I don't know.
Whatevs.
I guess I'm checking out my fits more than what's hiding underneath.
I look cute in my clothes now, so I'm sure I'll look cute in whatever the summer edition throws at me.
The skin-tight possibility does make me nervy, so that's not exactly super awesome.
I'm sorry, my beloved!
Ah!
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
No!
My biggest nightmare!
Is it actually tight on me?
This can't be right!
Have I betrayed my Shizuku-chan?
I'm sorry, my beloved!
No!
This one, too!
What happened?
Why the heck won't the girls cooperate?!
There. That's a dub.
Everything fits!
I guess I was just imagining things.
It's a little tight, but I just finished eating,
so no major worries there.
Ahh!
Are you for real?
You gained weight?
I'm shocked. Depresso espresso.
Wear it. You look exactly the same to me.
This explains why you didn't order your honey toast.
It's good that you're grabbing the diet by the horns.
Verdict is, even the great Maureen gains weight.
T.B.A.G.?
I did notice a microscopic difference
when you were changing into Rey's suit.
You look skinnier at the beach.
Just a teeny, but still the...
You just said so!
What the heck else are friends for?!
I didn't imagine it, so I thought I was imagining these pusses
I would have sounded like a prayer!
I don't really pay attention to other people's bodies.
I'm more interested in checking out their swimsuits.
Oh, I guess it didn't happen overnight, did it?
What a disaster!
Did Rey's endless suit not feel tight?
It fit great.
I don't understand what's happening to me.
Hold the phone.
You were wearing those sick undies.
Maybe they were sucking you in.
You're a naughty!
Oh!
Those undies are miracle workers.
You can see that.
This mega sucks.
I need to try for myself.
Even if I started gaining weight around the cultural festival,
I still have no clue how.
Leftover bento bites for breakfast,
a full bento for lunch,
emergency rations,
and fish at Gojo's place for dinner.
All that sounds pretty healthy, if you ask me.
I feel like crap.
I don't know where I went wrong.
Not a robber, just Maureen.
Come in!
It's sorry!
Now that's a full meal!
This looks so delicious.
I'm like totally starving.
Kotatsu time.
Perfectly toasty.
Toasty and tasty!
Kitagawa, do you prefer the section with or without the innards?
Without, I'll let you tackle all the bitter bits.
Could I interest you in some Daikon Orochi?
Yes, please!
It's dark, Al.
Huh?
Let me take care of the rest of the dishes this time.
You sure?
I probably should head home.
I'm sorry I didn't finish.
It's fine.
Let me walk you to the station.
Nah, that's okay.
I'll take the well-lit path.
Thanks, though.
For you, for the morning.
Another brekkie?
I'm so happy!
All I did was make a little extra.
You're the best.
Thanks, Gojo.
Sure thing.
Rice balls from the Takikomi Gohan!
It was stuffed to the gills with chickeny, mushroomy goodies!
I totes had seconds!
Packed me some kinipita with the rolled omelette, too!
Ahhhh...
It's still warm!
Gotta eat it while it's hot, bro!
Ahhhh...
It's all coming together...
You really gained weight?
You sure?
You looked the same!
I never noticed.
I'm not exactly the same.
My stomach is just a little bit...
Uh...
The worst part is that my clothes fit tighter.
Truth is...
Most of the outfits you made me...
I can't even zip them up anymore.
I'm sorry.
Cool. Let's just readjust the sizing.
So you're not angry?
No, of course not. Is there a reason I should be?
Well, yeah. You spent forever making those for me.
Sure, but sizing is supposed to fluctuate. It happens to everyone.
It doesn't happen to me because I'm going to lose the weight.
Outfits should stay the way they are.
All right. That's your call.
So I was thinking, no more cosplay until I lose weight.
I've been doing hella sit-ups since I realized the prob yesterday.
Plus, I started a diet.
A diet, huh?
Cosplay magazines always have articles about diets and getting in shape.
I assume they were for people who wanted to achieve a specific character's physique,
but that stuff could be useful if there are certain clothes you want to wear.
Well, I've been cooking pretty light.
So how did this change happen so suddenly?
Do you have any idea?
For the most part, the way you eat seems fairly healthy to me.
Yeah. When I'm around you, it's dandy.
The real damage happens when I get home. You feel me?
Are you eating sweets?
Close, but I go for something a bit heavier than that.
Heavier?
You're kidding.
I've been sending you home with breakfast.
It's four morning.
But you're eating it that night?
Mm-hmm.
Interesting.
Then what do you eat for breakfast?
Just the leftover bites that didn't make the bento.
What does that even mean?
Um-yum-yum.
More, please!
All right, if we combine the number of calories in each meal, we get about 50,000 calories per day.
It's just food! Why do you look so scared?
It's not that I'm scared. I'm just a bit surprised.
Your food is so gassed that I would feel crazy guilty to just stick it in the fridge.
Well, thank you.
On the bright side, if you make a couple simple changes, you should be back to normal soon.
Yay!
Huh?
Whoa! I feel better already!
Some good news?
Tomorrow. Meet me after school. You and I have got some shopping to do.
Sounds good. What are you buying?
You'll see.
Ta-da! Loose socks!
Those things are so long. People really wear these?
Some people wear them longer. They went up to 180 cm.
To do it proper, you're supposed to stretch them out first.
Here!
Pinch my foot a hand, will ya?
This feels so wrong. You just bought them.
It's part of the game.
According to Hikaru, the looser they are, the cuter they are.
Duh!
There.
And done!
These chips are so cute!
And they're pretty warm, too.
I know!
Take a pic of me, Gojo.
All right.
Here.
I'm so saving up for one of these.
They're mad pricey.
It's a fat check.
Huh?
Is that...
No way!
You bought the DSLR?
Uh-huh.
It got here yesterday!
I can't believe you got one!
I told you I'd buy it, so I did!
If Mama wants something, then Mama gets it!
Capiche?
She's so determined!
It came with two sick lenses!
The other is much bigger, so I started with this.
Chicken!
Isn't it wild?
I'm literally in love!
I've legit wanted life and can die happy!
I worked my butt off and did like a bajillion jobs
to bring this baby home!
Yeah, I'm like peak excited!
Hang on!
There are so many cameras available
and they all have different features.
Tell me, how did you decide on that one?
You want the lure?
I'm just as clueless as you are
when it comes to this stuff,
so I asked my girl Suzuka
what kind of camera she rocks.
I use the Kiss M mirrorless
and it cost me about 80,000 yen.
Huh?
About 80,000, huh?
Hold up.
Kiss M is such a cute name!
And the M stands for Maureen!
It's meant for me!
I need it!
It's totally fate!
Don't you think?
A lot had happened in the time he'd known Maureen,
but in that moment,
her determination shook Wakuna to his very core.
Okay, I think I figured out the basics enough
to take a quick picture.
Your girl is ready too!
Cheese!
I want to do a photo shoot with a new camera,
but I can't cosplay yet.
I figured a new hairstyle would help me feel sort of special.
Worth a shot.
So that's why you bought the loose socks, huh?
You got it, Goober!
Come on, Mr. Photographer!
Take a portrait!
I'll try.
Now where would portrait mode be?
Oh, hey!
Ready, set, go!
What's wrong?
I, uh...
It's amazing!
The quality's incredible!
Wow!
When you zoom in, it's just as clear!
You're so hyped up!
I think you're more into it than me!
I might be.
Ah!
It's just so awesome!
I know high-quality cameras are supposed to take high-quality pictures,
but I'm a complete and utter amateur!
The fact that I can take incredible photos like this
could seriously make me cry!
It's so much fun.
Cameras at a whole new layer!
We're not done yet, dude!
Right.
Well, do I look good?
I love that you're loving this!
Another one?
I'm so glad I bought it!
I know I'm on a big diet right now,
but once I'm done with all that,
you and I should toads grab some monja.
I'd love to go while we're on winter break!
I'll message the gang to see if they're down, too.
I need some mentai cheese mochi monja in my belly like yesterday!
Do you get cravings?
Of course you do!
Cheesy stuff is my craving of choice.
We'll need to make reservations ASAP.
It's so not cool to pull up to a restaurant
with nine high schoolers out of the blue.
We should try out the food mode later.
No calories in a pic?
Capture those delicious memories!
Let's test out the other lens.
It's for super far away shots.
I'm curious to find out just how far I can get.
It is called kiss-em, after all.
I'd lose that move in music bits.
Did my sonic zoom scare you?
I'm sorry about that.
I swear I didn't mean to blur up your artistry.
I'm ready to be serious now.
You wait right there!
I'll get extra far away!
It came out crystal clear.
The photo quality is almost too high!
I gotta watch the faces I pull.
The bouquet effect is so pretty!
I'm glad you figured it out!
You mentioned liking it before, and now I can see why.
Oh yeah!
There's a cosplay event this weekend.
I kinda feel like it would be fun to go as a photographer this time.
Apparently Amadei is gonna be there.
I have to go!
He's cosplaying Hokuto Neon, and I would literally keel over if I didn't get to experience all that cuteness in person!
Suzuka should be there too, so I'm extra hyped!
Yeah, I was planning to go myself.
For real?
Hold on, Kojo.
Are you gonna cosplay?
You better show me, show me, show me, show me!
It's not bad!
Show me now, show me now, show me now!
I would have told you!
Back during the last event, when we went to ACOS, I noticed something called Cosboard.
I looked it up, and it's popular for making props.
Oh, I've seen lots of prop masters use that.
I'd never heard of it, so I did some research.
Look at this.
Whoa!
That's like so heaven cool!
I completely agree!
I still can't get over those tiny details on the katana!
The artist who posted this is named Akira, and he has tons of videos that shed light on the whole prop-making process.
Wow!
I was watching his page like a hawk.
I wanted to ask him some specific questions, but I was scared to bother him.
Instead, I tried to take as much info from his clips as I could.
But soon, the videos weren't enough, and I had to reach out!
Just to say I liked his work!
It's too good to be true, but he responded!
He was actually super nice!
Shit, dude!
No wonder you've been in such a good mood.
Now you know!
I'm over the moon about it!
He said he'll be there this weekend, and said I could say hi!
Dang, Gojo!
You love this Akira guy!
Yeah!
There's just so much I'd like to ask him!
Also, if you're on socials now, you should have told me!
I want to follow you, doofus!
But I haven't posted anything.
I made an account so I could contact him.
Gotta start somewhere!
Good point.
Here are mine.
Hey, is it cool if we head to your place after this?
Of course!
Would you like to join us for dinner?
You know it!
But I've got other plans, too.
There's something that I'm dying to capture with the new camera!
Look right into the lens!
Ready, and...
Oh, my!
Who is that handsome devil?
This is a fancy camera, Maureen.
You must have worked hard for it.
Good for you.
You're sweet, but I don't think I'm worthy of being your first model.
You are!
I came here specifically to take that pick.
Give me a round of applause.
Bye!
мин
Thank you.
Next time.